Deepa Divakar Hegde

Software Engineer

Who am I?

Skilled and efficient iOS and UI Developer with 2 years of experience in creating unique and modern applications. Looking forward to work in challenging areas and strive for excellence in all my endeavors. Bring out blend innovation and uniqueness in my work and make a mark in the field of technology. Hardworking, with the good Communication Skills.

2

Years of Experience

4

Projects Involved

Experience

TEKsystems Global Services(July 2018- Present)

2018 - 2020

- Efficiently worked with iOS team from planning, designing, integrating the UI with api's, QA Testing, Code freezing to Deployment using Swift & SwiftUI with Agile development process.
- Responsible for Designing & Developing several adaptive, reusable Ul's components with auto-layouts (Storyboards, Xibs, Programmatically)
- Designed abstract object model classes & worked with iOS frameworks such as Core-Data, Core-Location, Core-Animations, MapKit, UIKit, AVFondation, Cocoa Touch, SceneKit, app state container in Swift.
- Populated the data in Views By integrating Restful APIs
- Implemented third party libraries, Cocoa Pods and APIs.
- Performed in-app caching using Realm.
- Worked with Design Patterns like Singleton, MVC & MVVM.
- Involved in resolving Bugs, writing test cases using XCTests & app monitoring using Fabric and New Relic.

2020 - Present

- Developed web Application from scratch using Angular 8 (MEAN STACK) with Angular Material and more libraries.
- Have taken major part in UI/UX design process by giving design ideas for the application & implemented OAuth mechanism.
- Created basic REST APIs using NodeJS.
- Understanding the Requirements & Breaking up the requirements into small implementable modules for development.

Personal Info

Email

deepah96@gmail.com

Phone

+91 - 9535488280

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/deepahegde-b238bb131

Skills

Languages & Frameworks

SWIFT

SWIFTUI

Objective C - Basics

HTML

CSS

Angular & Angular JS

NodeJS - Basics

MongoDB

MEAN STACK

GIT

IDEs & Deployment Tools

XCode

Fabric

TestFlight

Visual Studio Code

Postman

JIRA

Education

2014-2018

Computer Science & Engineering Bapuji Institute of Engineering & Technology